A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1982-1983
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series III: Permanent Files
  - Physics(NEAL)--Southern Universities Research Association (SURA) IV (1 of 2) 1982Jan-1983Jan (Box 35)
  - Physics(NEAL)--Southern Universities Research Association (SURA) IV (2 of 2) 1982Jan-1983Jan (Box 36)
  - Physics(NEAL)--Southern Universities Research Association (SURA) V (2 folders) 1983 Feb-Jun (Box 36)
  - Physics(NEAL)--Southern Universities Research Association (SURA) VI (2 folders) 1983Jun-1984Jan (Box 36)
  - Ad Hoc Committee--Search for Dean of Admissions 1984 Dec (Box 37)
  - Ad Hoc Committee--Darden School Dean Search 1982-1983 (Box 37)
  - Ad Hoc Committee--School of Education Deanship Search 1983 (Box 37)
  - Ad Hoc Committee--Engineering and Applied Sciences Dean Search 1983Apr-1984Feb (Box 37)
  - Ad Hoc Committee--Search for Dean of Faculty of Arts and Sciences 1984Sep-1985Jan (Box 37)
  - Ad Hoc Committee--University Telephone System II 1981Jul-1982Aug (Box 37)
  - Ad Hoc Committee--Telephone Weekly Telephone Progress Reports 1982 Jan-Jun (Box 37)
  - Special Committee--Acquisition of Research Laboratory 1982 Feb-Mar (Box 37)
  - Special Committee--Alderman Library Building Security and Fir Protection System 1980Jan-1982Mar (Box 37)
  - Special Committee--Birdwood Golf Course 1979Sep-1982Mar (Box 37)
  - Special Committee--Blue Ridge Hospital Renovation ( 1of 2) 1977Mar-1982Jun (Box 37)
  - Special Committee--Blue Ridge Hospital Renovation (2 of 2) 1977Mar-1982Jun (Box 38)
  - Special Committee--Chemistry Building/ Energy Conservation and Modification 1981Oct-1982Jun (Box 38)
  - Special Committee--Clemons Library Terrace Landscaping 1982 Jul (Box 38)
  - Special Committee--Clinch Valley College Student Housing 1982 Mar-May (Box 38)
  - Special Committee--Clinical Chemistry 1980Jul-1984May (Box 38)
  - Special Committee--Darden Research Center 1981Feb-1982Jul (Box 38)
  - Special Committee--Energy Management Control System/Expansion Upgrade 1981Oct-1982Mar (Box 38)
  - Special Committee--Fraternity/Sorority Task Force 1982 Feb-Mar (Box 38)
  - Special Committee--Gilmer Hall Asbestos Removal 1982 Jul (Box 38)
  - Special Committee--Gilmer Hall Electrical System 1981 Sep-Dec (Box 38)
  - Special Committee--Halsey Hall Renovation, Phase I 1982 Apr (Box 38)
  - Special Committee--Handicapped Building 1977Oct-1982Jul (Box 38)
  - Special Committee--Hospital Nursing Service Action 1982 May-Jul (Box 38)
  - Special Committee--Jordan Hall/Energy Conservation and Modification 1981Oct-1982Mar (Box 38)
  - Special Committee--Madison Hall 1978May-1984Sep (Box 38)
  - Special Committee--Modernization of Thornton Hall 1983 Apr 19 (Box 38)
  - Special Committee--Monroe Hall Pre-Planning Study 1982 Aug-Sep (Box 38)
  - Special Committee--Observatory Dining Hall Addition 1982 Jul 1 (Box 38)
  - Special Committee--Pathology/Neurology Cancer Research Laboratory Building Committee 1980 Jul 16 (Box 38)
  - Special Committee--Pediatric Newborn Intensive Care Unit 1982 May-Jul (Box 38)
  - Special Committee--Police Building 1980Jun-1982Mar (Box 38)
  - Special Committee--Printing Services Building 1982 Mar-May (Box 39)
  - Special Committee--Real Estate Task Force 1982 Feb 15 (Box 39)
  - Special Committee--Renovation and Modernization of Building #203 1982Oct-1983Apr (Box 39)
  - Special Committee--Scott Stadium Multi-Purpose Annex 1976Apr-1982May (Box 39)
  - Special Committee--Sears Building 1982 Dec (Box 39)
  - Special Committee--Special Materials Handling Facility 1981Oct-1982Jul (Box 39)
  - Special Committee--Sponsors Hall Addition 1981Feb-1982Jul (Box 39)
  - Special Committee--Sprinkler/Smoke Detection System 1978Jan-1981Aug (Box 39)
  - Special Committee--Stadium Road/Student Housing Building (2 folders) 1980Nov-1983Apr (Box 39)
  - Special Committee--Student Activity Building 1982 Apr-Sep (Box 39)
  - Special Committee--Student Health Building 1981 Feb-Jun (Box 39)
  - Special Committee--Student Housing--300Bed 1982May-1984Feb (Box 39)
  - Special Committee--Student Housing--500 Bed 1981 Feb (Box 39)
  - Special Committee--Water Distribution/ Fire Protection System II 1980Jun-1982Jun (Box 39)
- Series IV: Restricted Material (Box 40)